<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Make Jar Not War</title>
    <link>http://www.makejarnotwar.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Make Jar Not War</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2020</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 04:47:35 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.makejarnotwar.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Nate Schutta</title>
      <link>http://www.makejarnotwar.com/posts/nschutta/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 04:47:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.makejarnotwar.com/posts/nschutta/</guid>
      <description>Bio Nathaniel T. Schutta (@ntschutta) is a software architect focused on cloud computing and building usable applications. A proponent of polyglot programming, Nate has written multiple books and appeared in several videos. Nate is a seasoned speaker regularly presenting at conferences worldwide, No Fluff Just Stuff symposia, meetups, universities, and user groups. In addition to his day job, Nate is an adjunct professor at the University of Minnesota where he teaches students to embrace dynamic languages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jakub Pilimon</title>
      <link>http://www.makejarnotwar.com/posts/jpilimon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 04:47:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.makejarnotwar.com/posts/jpilimon/</guid>
      <description>Bio Jakub is Spring Developer Advocate at VMware, blogger, passionate programmer and trainer. He loves to tackle complex enterprises with Domain Driven Design, Test Driven Development and Spring. Being a microservice freak, architecture is his main area of interest too. When he does not program he rides motorbike, skis or grows his beard. Also, here is his DZone MVB awarded blog: pillopl.github.io</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paul Czarkowski</title>
      <link>http://www.makejarnotwar.com/posts/pczarkowski/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 04:47:19 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.makejarnotwar.com/posts/pczarkowski/</guid>
      <description>Bio Paul helps people be more awesome by helping to close the gap between the various teams in the IT organization from Development to Operations to Security and everyone in between.
Paul has over 20 years of experience running IT systems, ranging from small startups like Bluebox to large video games publishers like Electronic Arts where honed his skills in Operations and Automation before moving into his current role.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tiffany Jernigan</title>
      <link>http://www.makejarnotwar.com/posts/tjernigan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 04:47:07 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.makejarnotwar.com/posts/tjernigan/</guid>
      <description>Bio Tiffany is a senior developer advocate at VMware in Seattle and is focused on the realm of Kubernetes. She mostly recently was working as a software developer and developer advocate (nerd whisperer) for containers in AWS. She also formerly worked at Docker and Intel. Prior to that, she graduated from Georgia Tech with a degree in electrical engineering. In her free time she likes to spend time with her fiancé, family, and friends as well as dabble in photography.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robert Brindley</title>
      <link>http://www.makejarnotwar.com/posts/rbrindley/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 04:47:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.makejarnotwar.com/posts/rbrindley/</guid>
      <description>Bio With a strong history in delivering technical data to live audiences, Bob is an advocate on the VMware advocacy Team. Bob is a savvy veteran of the convention scene. You can find him at most of the events that VMware graces around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cora Iberkleid</title>
      <link>http://www.makejarnotwar.com/posts/ciberkleid/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 04:46:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.makejarnotwar.com/posts/ciberkleid/</guid>
      <description>Bio Cora Iberkleid is an Advisory Cloud Application and Platform Architect at VMware, where she helps enterprises leverage modern technologies like Spring Boot, Spring Cloud, and Cloud Foundry in order to deliver better quality software faster. Prior to joining VMware, she spent nearly a decade designing and building enterprise integration applications as part of the Professional Services organizations at Sun Microsystems and Oracle. She has previously spoken at SpringOne Platform, SpringOne Tour, SpringConnect, deliver:Agile, Cloud Native New York and New York City Spring User Group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coté</title>
      <link>http://www.makejarnotwar.com/posts/cote/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 04:46:36 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.makejarnotwar.com/posts/cote/</guid>
      <description>Bio Michael Coté works at VMware on the advocate team. He’s been an industry analyst at RedMonk and 451 Research, worked in corporate strategy and M&amp;amp;A at Dell in software and cloud, and was a programmer for a decade before all that. He does several weekly (mostly) tech podcasts, writes a column on Agile &amp;amp; DevOps for The Register, blogs at Cote.io, and is @cote in Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark Heckler</title>
      <link>http://www.makejarnotwar.com/posts/mheckler/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 04:46:36 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.makejarnotwar.com/posts/mheckler/</guid>
      <description>Bio Mark Heckler is a Professional Problem Solver and Spring Developer &amp;amp; Advocate at VMware, conference speaker, published author, &amp;amp; Java Champion focusing upon developing innovative production-ready software at velocity for the Cloud. He has worked with key players in the manufacturing, retail, medical, scientific, telecom, and financial industries and various public sector organizations to develop and deliver critical capabilities on time and on budget. Mark is an open source contributor (Spring Security and numerous other projects), author/curator of a developer-focused blog at https://thehecklers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Josh Long</title>
      <link>http://www.makejarnotwar.com/posts/jlong/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 04:38:55 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.makejarnotwar.com/posts/jlong/</guid>
      <description>Bio Josh is a Spring Developer Advocate at Pivotal. Josh is a Java Champion, author of 5 books (including O&amp;rsquo;Reilly&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Cloud Native Java: Designing Resilient Systems with Spring Boot, Spring Cloud, and Cloud Foundry&amp;rdquo;) and 3 best-selling video trainings (including &amp;ldquo;Building Microservices with Spring Boot Livelessons&amp;rdquo; w/ Phil Webb), and an open-source contributor (Spring Boot, Spring Integration, Spring Cloud, Activiti and Vaadin).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mario Gray</title>
      <link>http://www.makejarnotwar.com/posts/mgray/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 04:38:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.makejarnotwar.com/posts/mgray/</guid>
      <description>Bio Mr. Gray is a Principal Technologist at Pivotal with over 20 years of experience in software development, software architecture. He is co-author of Apress&amp;rsquo;s Pro Spring Integration. He’s helped organizations large and small build service-based architectures in a number of different runtimes and platforms over the decades, but adopting Spring in 2004, and using it whenever possible since, was a no-brainer that culminated in joining the Spring team in 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>